(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-02T00:12:10.375294",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
RosaMiA Acoustic Live 告知あり
RosaMiA Acoustic Live [Announcement Included]
パレ...
Parade...
パレパレパレ
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal.
パレパレパレ
Parade, parade, parade!
探しに行く
Let's go search!
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as we want.
ただ独り言 綴った
I just wrote down my monologues.
ただ始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted it to begin.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
A light turned on far away in the darkness.
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name that was far too dazzling.
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Those were memories that were far too kind.
もっと近づいてと手を伸ばした
I reached out to get closer,
思いがけず結びあった
and we unexpectedly connected.
ほら今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now we have become the lost ones.
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Shine bright!
悔しさも愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustrations and your dearest things.
風 夢 晴れ 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, and clear skies—we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは光
A humble prayer becomes light.
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can hold my head high for having found you.
ここから これから アワプライ パレパレ
From here on, from now on, our pride! Parade, parade!
まだ頼りない予感を
Let's sing of this still-unreliable
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
premonition. There's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も 解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world that no one can unravel.
いつか また会えるおまじない
A spell to ensure we meet again someday.
あの日のゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that started from zero that day.
数えきれないことの数々
Countless events,
数えるような思い出じゃないさ
but they aren't memories you can simply count.
ほら今 僕らをひとつと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call ourselves one.
パレパレパレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's beautiful!
許しあえる刹那 夜はきらめく
In the fleeting moments we forgive each other, the night sparkles.
雨 晴れ ハレ また隣 空
Rain, sun, sunshine, and once again, the sky beside us.
ふさわしい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
A journey worthy of us is one walked with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's walking with you.
ただいまを聞けば
If I hear "I'm home,"...
おかえりって叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to be taken for granted.
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Shine bright!
暗がりを満たすのは君だ、僕だ
The ones who fill the darkness are you and I.
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Shine bright!
悔しさも愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustrations and your dearest things.
風 夢 晴れ 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, and clear skies—we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは光
A humble prayer becomes light.
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign.
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in together with you, it's a wonderful start.
ここから これから アワプライ パレパレ
From here on, from now on, our pride! Parade, parade!
アワプライ パレパレ
Our pride! Parade, parade!
ということで！
And with that...
RosaMiAアコースティックライブ、始まりましたー！
The RosaMiA Acoustic Live has officially begun!
イェーイ！
Yay!
どうでしたか？
How was that?
1曲目からね
Right from the first song...
アワプライパレパレとか
Yeah, from "Our Pride, Parade, Parade"...
なんかさ、こういう感じでこの曲歌ったことなかったから
We've never sung this song in this style before,
そう、ドキドキしちゃった
so my heart was pounding!
ドキドキしながらね
With pounding hearts...
わかる
I know.
三声になってましたね、はい
It turned into a three-part harmony, didn't it? Yes!
なんか最後ポーズ決めるの忘れてたよね、ちょっと
I think we kind of forgot to do the final pose at the end, just a bit.
集中しすぎて
We were too focused.
歌に集中しすぎて、ちょっと忘れてたかも
Focused too much on the singing, so maybe we forgot it for a moment.
そんなこともありながらね、はい
Well, with things like that happening too... Yes.
あ、もうすでに...
Oh, already...
え？なになと？
What? What was that?
えー、こちらハッシュタグのトレンドで...
Um, on the trending hashtags...
3位に入ってるらしい！
...we're apparently in 3rd place!
何？！すごい！ありがとう！
What?! Amazing! Thank you!
とりあえずちょっと自己紹介しましょうか。
Anyway, shall we do some self-introductions?
じゃあ、ちょっとよろしくお願いします。
Well then, please go ahead.
では、自己紹介させていただきます。
Now, let us introduce ourselves.
ロザミアの「ロザ」担当、アキ・ローゼンタールです！
In charge of the "Rosa" in RosaMiA, I'm Aki Rosenthal!
はろはろはろー！あろーなー！
Haro-haro-haro! Alona!
そして！
And next!
はい！ロザミアの「ミ」担当、長女の大神ミオです！
Hi! In charge of the "Mi" in RosaMiA, the eldest daughter, Ookami Mio!
よろしくお願いします！
Pleasure to meet you!
いえいいえいいえい！そして！
Yay yay yay! And next!
はい！ロザミアの「ア」担当、末っ子のAZKiです！
Yes! In charge of the "A" in RosaMiA, the youngest, AZKi!
こんあづきー！よろしくお願いします！
Kon-AZKi! Nice to meet you!
なんか、生き生きと末っ子してるんだよね、この空間にいると。
You seem to play the youngest role so energetically in this space.
この3人だとね、末っ子でいられる。幸せです。ありがとうございます！
With these three, I can be the youngest. I'm happy. Thank you!
長女、次女、末っ子。
Eldest sister, second sister, and the youngest child.
長女、次女、末っ子、でやらせていただいて...
Playing the roles of eldest, second, and youngest...
3姉妹でやらせていただいております！
...we perform as three sisters!
というわけで、この3人でロザミアというグループをやらせていただいているんですけども...
And so, the three of us are active as the group RosaMiA...
なんとですね、このロザミアでライブをするのは、今回初めてということで！
...but actually, this is the very first time we are performing a live concert as RosaMiA!
初！
The first!
しかも、生歌唱のライブということでね。
And it's a live-singing concert.
3人でいっぱい練習しましたね！
The three of us practiced a lot!
練習しました！
We did!
合宿のように！
Like a training camp!
部活みたいでさ、楽しかった！
It felt like club activities, it was fun!
部活だね。合唱部みたいな感じでね。
Yeah, club activities. Like a choir club.
たくさん練習したのでね。たくさん練習した1曲目、どうでしたでしょうか？
Since we practiced so much, how was our first song?
「一番難しいまであるか？」って言われて、いや、そんなことはない！
Someone said "Is it even the hardest one?", but no, that's not true!
そんなことはなかった。でもかなり難しい方ではあったよね。
It wasn't that, but it was on the harder side.
パート分けでしたよね。
The division of parts was tough, right?
そうそう、パート分けが難しかったかも。
Yeah, partitioning the parts might have been hard.
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
というわけで、トレンドが3位にも入っているという情報ですが...
Anyway, we have news that we're trending 3rd...
はい、ハッシュタグはこちらになっております！
...and yes, here is our hashtag!
「#RosaMiAアコースティックライブ」というタグで、皆さんどしどしXでポストしてくださいね！
With the tag "#RosaMiAアコースティックライブ", please post lots on X!
よろしくお願いします！
Please and thank you!
後でエゴサするので。
We'll ego-search later.
頑張ったのでね、応援だったり、感想だったりをハッシュタグつけてたくさん盛り上げてくれたら...
We worked hard, so write your support and impressions with the hashtag to hype it up...
見たい見たい！
We want to see them!
ロザミア知らない人にも届けたいですよね。
We also want to reach people who don't know RosaMiA yet.
お願いします！
Please do!
「今2位になってるよ」って！
Someone said, "We are 2nd now!"
ええ？！2位？！すごすぎる！
What?! 2nd?! That's too amazing!
ありがとうございます！ぜひぜひいっぱいポストしてね！
Thank you so much! Please keep posting a lot!
つーわけでですね...
And so...
どんどん行っちゃうんですか？それとも永遠にここでトークしてるんですか？
Are we moving right along, or are we chatting here forever?
え、ちょっとさ...
Um, well...
お水飲む？
Should we drink some water?
お水飲もうかな？
Maybe I should drink some water.
ちょっと一瞬お水飲ませてくださいね。
Please let us take a quick water break.
お水おいしい、おいしい。
Water is delicious.
いや、一瞬お水飲ませてくださいと言いつつ...
While saying "let us take a quick water break,"...
次は、もうそろそろ次の曲いっちゃいますか？
...shall we get going with the next song soon?
いっちゃいます？
Shall we?
というわけで次の曲は、ミオとアキちゃんの二人ということで！
So, the next song is by the duo of Mio and Aki-chan!
こっから二人ずつ歌っていくんですね。
From here on, we'll be singing in pairs.
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
じゃあ、二人は準備お願いします！
Then, please get ready, you two!
あづちゃんもお水飲んでもらったところ恐縮なんですけども、MCを...
AZKi-chan, sorry right after you got a drink of water, but could you handle the MC...
二人がね、準備しておりますので。
...while the two of them are preparing?
はーい！みんな、ロザミアのアコースティックライブ来てくれてありがとう！
Hi! Everyone, thank you for coming to RosaMiA's acoustic live!
1曲目いかがでしたか？
How did you like the first song?
「Our Bright Parade」
"Our Bright Parade."
今回ぜひアレンジにも注目していただきたいなと。
I'd love for you to pay attention to the arrangement this time.
いつもと違うおしゃれなアレンジになっておりますので。
It's a stylish arrangement that's different from usual.
そこもそれと合わせて、3人のハーモニーを聴いていただけたらなと思います！
Along with that, I hope you enjoyed listening to our three-way harmony!
お、というところで、二人の準備ができたみたいなので！
Oh, and with that, it looks like the two of them are ready!
それでは、聴いていただきましょう。
So, let's have you listen to...
「JANE DOE」
..."JANE DOE."
JANE DOE
[Title: JANE DOE]
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It's almost as if we're the only two in this world, isn't it?
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
How... I just ended up dreaming a little, that's all.
つま先に月明かり 花束の香りに保存
Moonlight at our toes, with the scent of a bouquet...
指に触れる指
fingers touching fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I have to go now...
何もかも
leaving everything behind.
…忘れて
...forget me.
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of shattered glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
with every step of pain, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come to see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish being released into a rusted pool,
靴箱の中 隠したリンゴ
an apple hidden inside the shoe locker.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷は
The scar remaining on your withered skin...
灯籠のように 浮かんだ迷子
...is like a lantern, a floating lost child.
どこにいるの？ （ここにいるよ）
Where are you? (I'm right here)
何をしてるの？ （ずっと見てるよ）
What are you doing? (I'm watching you always)
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side,
遊びに来てよ
come play with me.
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of shattered glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
with every step of pain, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come to see me.
まるでこの世界で
It's almost as if
二人だけみたいだね
we're the only two in this world,
なんて
just...
少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
a tiny dream I ended up having.
はーい
Yay!
はあー
Whew!
歌い切ったー！
We sang our hearts out!
いや、やっぱり素敵な曲だよね
Man, this is such a lovely song after all.
本当だね
It really is.
というわけで、アキちゃんと、うちの「JANE DOE」でした！
And with that, this was Aki-chan and me singing "JANE DOE"!
わー！ めちゃくちゃ素敵！ ありがとう！
Yay! That was absolutely wonderful! Thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ああ、ちょっと緊張した
Ah, I was a bit nervous.
緊張した？ そんなこと感じさせない歌声でしたよ、二人とも
You were nervous? Your singing voices didn't show that at all, both of you!
ありがとう！ 本当に！
Thank you so much, really!
すごかった
It was amazing.
なんかね、なんかこの曲は、ま、
You know, for this song...
二人ずつね、これから歌ってくんだろうな、みたいにうっすら思ってるかもしれないんですけど
you might vaguely expect that we'll keep singing it in pairs from here on out...
はいはいはい
Right, right.
けど、どうですか？ どこが難しかったですか？ この曲は
But how did you find it? Which parts did you find difficult?
えー！
Oh, boy!
え、でもやっぱりハモりがさ、原曲より少し多めに、こうハモる場所を作っていって
Well, we added a bit more harmony parts than the original version has.
確かに
That's true.
そこ、やっぱり掛け合いとか、こう合わせるみたいなのとかを…
So having that back-and-forth and syncing up...
呼吸感とか？
Like matching your breathing?
呼吸感とか、うん。でもね、
Yeah, like the breathing. But you see,
あの、アキちゃんが多分以前、あのアキちゃんのライブで「JANE DOE」やってるからか分からないけど
I don't know if it's because Aki-chan sang "JANE DOE" before during her own live show,
ほぼ完璧だったわけ
but she was almost perfect.
いやいやいや
No, no, no!
いや、そんなことないよー
No, that's not true!
もう最初から出来上がってて
She was ready to go right from the start.
あの、練習しなきゃいけないのうちだったわけ
I was actually the one who needed to practice!
うちだったわけ？
You were?
うちだったわけ
Yes, me!
アキロゼの生誕祭で、あの
At my birthday festival,
ミオちゃんパートのメロディを歌らせてもらったことがあって
I had the chance to sing Mio-chan's melody part.
そう、そう
Right, right.
今回はこっちの百鬼さんパートは、初めての挑戦だったんだけど
So Nakiri-san's part was a new challenge for me this time.
あ、そうなんだ！
Oh, really?
雰囲気とかはね
But the overall vibe, you know...
いや、分かってたからもう最初からほぼ完璧で
No, you already had it down, so it was perfect from the start.
いやいや、そんなことないですよ
No, no, that's really not true.
うちはあわあわあわあわってしてて
I was the one scrambling like "awa awa..."
めちゃくちゃ素敵なね、声の伸びだったよ
You had such a wonderfully extended vocal range!
いや、ハモれてすごい楽しかった！
Singing in harmony was so much fun!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ちょっと緊張したけど、かなりミオちゃんのね、ハーモニーに助けられたというか
I was a bit nervous, but Mio-chan's harmony really helped me a lot.
ハモり上手いからさ、ミオちゃん
You're so good at harmonizing, Mio-chan.
上手いのよ、ミオちゃん
She really is good!
ありがとうございます。先生の…
Thank you so much. I'm like a teacher's...
ハモリスト
Hamorist (harmony expert).
ハモリスト、ハモり好きだもんね
Hamorist! You do love harmonizing.
はい、まだまだ精進させていただきますが
Yes, I still have a lot of room to improve, though!
じゃあ、じゃあ、そろそろ、あれですかね？
Well then, is it about that time?
え？ え？ もう行っちゃうんですか？
What? Already? You're leaving already?
え、まだ引っ張って、話すなら漫談始めますけど
Well, if you want to stretch it out, I can start a comedy talk routine.
漫談始まっちゃう！
A comedy talk routine?!
まあ、そろそろね、次の…
Well, it's about time to...
準備ってことで、ミオちゃんとあやめちゃんに歌ってもらうので、アキロゼはこちらのほうに…
get ready for the next song by Mio-chan and Ayame-chan, so AkiRoze will head off-stage...
いってらっしゃーい
See you later!
準備よし、衣装よし。
Ready, outfits look good.
頑張ろう、はつちゃん。頑張ろうね。
Let's do our best, Hatsu-chan. Yes, let's!
緊張するよ、ちょちょ。
I'm nervous, Chocho.
緊張するね。
We really are nervous.
ちょっとお水飲もうっか。
Let's drink some water.
お水飲んでね。
Make sure to drink some water.
はい、二人ともお水飲んでもらって。
Alright, while both of them drink some water,
じゃあ、その間にやこはちょっとコメントあれしようかな。
Yako will read some of the comments.
「草」っていう文字がすごく、あの、黄緑で目立って拾いやすいなと思うんですけど。
The word "lol" in light green stands out so much that it's easy to spot.
こっちのが自作です。
This one is self-made.
あ、そうなの？
Oh, really?
そうですね。可愛いスタンプ！
Yes, it is. What a cute stamp!
いや、でもね、こうやってみんなも、なんか結構「待ってたよ」
But really, seeing everyone say "I've been waiting,"
「RosaMiAのライブ嬉しい」っていう声も見てたので。すごいありがとうございます。
and "I'm so happy for RosaMiA's live" makes me so grateful. Thank you!
ちょっと緊張して、初挑戦なのでね。
We're a bit nervous, since this is our first challenge.
あの、色々と頑張るっていう、そこであの、やってますので、応援よろしくお願いします。
We're going to try our hardest, so please support us.
では、二人は準備できたみたいなので、
Well, it looks like the two of them are ready,
次の曲、聴いていただきましょう。
so let's listen to the next song.
「夜光通信」
"Yakou Tsuushin" (Night Light Communication)
聞こえますか
Can you hear me?
夜光通信
[Title: Yakou Tsuushin]
ハロー ハロー 聞こえますか
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
そっちは何年？
What year is it over there?
新しく交わす手段は
The means to newly communicate...
ひとつじゃないさ
...is not just one.
漂う時間はどこへ行くのか
Where does the drifting time go?
サヨナラはいつ誰が決めるの
Who decides when "goodbye" is, and when?
その手に触れようと願ってる
I pray to touch that hand...
本当さ
...truly.
永久の夜光 君に歌う
I sing of the eternal night light to you
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is mean to you
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind
瞼の裏 ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind your eyelids, we can always meet again
穏やかに 健やかに
Calmly, healthily,
奏でるブーケ 君だって私だって
Playing a bouquet, both for you and for me
消えるのは言葉だけ
Only the words will disappear
ふんわり君を 抱きしめてあげるからね
Because I will gently embrace you
泣かないで
Please don't cry
延々と続く今日は
This endlessly continuing today
雪原のようで
Is like a snowfield
突然の幸せまでも
Blinding even...
眩ませるんだ
...sudden happiness.
忘れないで
Don't forget
どこでだって繋がる回線
A line that connects anywhere
寂しい宇宙とオレンジの公園
A lonely universe and an orange park
したしい心の限りに
To the absolute limit of our familiar hearts,
歌おう
Let's sing.
永久の夜光 届くよね
The eternal night light reaches you, right?
幻想よりも優しい形のまま
Remaining in a form gentler than an illusion
濡れそぼる その頬を
Those drenched cheeks,
こっそり撫でて 乾かしてあげるからね
I'll gently caress and dry them for you
何度だって
Over and over again
永久の夜光 此処に歌う
I sing of the eternal night light here
逢いたいよ 消えたくだなんてないよ
I want to see you, I don't want to disappear!
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind
今此処で 笑い合ったことを
That we laughed together here and now
永久の夜光 君に歌う
I sing of the eternal night light to you
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is mean to you
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind
瞼の裏 ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind your eyelids, we can always meet again
サヨナラは
Goodbyes are...
...goodbyes...
ねぇ 誰が 決めるもの
...hey, who decides them?
消えるのは
What disappears...
ふわり君を 抱きしめてあげるからね
Because I'll gently hold you close,
泣かないで
so please don't cry.
と、いうわけで！
And with that!
「夜光通信」歌わせていただきました！
We just performed "Night Light Communication"!
わー！「夜光通信」！ありがとうございます！
Wow! "Night Light Communication"! Thank you so much!
いやー、すごくね、素敵できき入ってたんですけど、あの、なんと嬉しいお知らせが届いてまして！
Wow, it was so wonderful that I was totally captivated. But guess what? We have some exciting news!
なんと！何ですか？何ですか？
Really? What is it? What is it?
あの、トレンド1位を、こちら！
We reached number one on the trending topics! Look at this!
ハッシュタグで獲得いたしました！ありがとうございます！やったー！
We achieved it with our hashtag! Thank you so much! Yay!
嬉しい！みんなのおかげ！
I'm so happy! It's all thanks to everyone!
みんなのおかげ！RosaMIAの名を届かせて...
Thanks to everyone! Making the name of RosaMIA resonate...
とどろかせて！嬉しいね、日曜日なのにすごい！
...and letting it ring out! I'm so happy, this is amazing for a Sunday!
ねー、嬉しい、ありがとうみんな！
Right? We're so happy! Thank you, everyone!
みんなのね、あの、コメントでも、アレンジがその、アコースティックバージョンすごい良いっていう
Everyone is saying in the comments that the acoustic arrangement is really nice,
コメントがたくさんあったし、やっぱりハーモニーがすごく綺麗って
there are so many comments like that, and that the harmony is beautiful too.
すごくみんなね、言ってくれてて
That's what everyone is telling us.
嬉しいな！でも上手に入ってたよね！
I'm so glad! But it really came together well!
入ってたよね！うん、できたできた！
It really did! Yes, we did it!
なんか向かい合ってさ、歌ってるとことか、なんかゾクゾクしたよね！
Singing while facing each other like that, it gave me shivers!
ゾクゾクした！なんかこう、ぞわっとした！
It gave me goosebumps! A real thrill!
実はですね、こちらの選曲はアズちゃんがしてくれまして
Actually, Azu-chan was the one who chose this song.
はい、私！今回はミオちゃんのね、枠でやらせていただくということもあり、僭越ながら
Yes, me! Since we're doing this on Mio-chan's channel today, I took the liberty,
やはり、もう、この曲大好きすぎて、ミオちゃんの「夜光通信」を
because I just love Mio-chan's "Night Light Communication" way too much.
歌いまくってて、すいません
I've been singing it all the time, sorry about that!
いやいや、嬉しいんですけどね、なんか本人よりも歌ってるという噂がある
No, no, I'm glad! Though there is a rumor that you sing it more than the original singer does.
噂されてる？マジ？
Is that rumor going around? Really?
印象的にね、なんかアズキちゃん今日も歌ってる、今日も歌ってるって
It feels like "Azuki-chan is singing it again today, and today too."
今日も歌ってるって、今日も言われてる
"She's singing it today as well," that's what they say.
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいんだけどね、本当に！ありがとうございます！
No, it makes me super happy, honestly! Thank you so much!
いや、でもかなりその、今回アコースティックアレンジでより、なんか曲の良さも伝わったんじゃないかな？
But with this acoustic arrangement, I feel like the song's charm was brought out even more, don't you think?
良さがね、より強調されてたよね！歌詞も素敵ですし
Its charm was definitely enhanced! The lyrics are so lovely, too.
よかった、本当に。聴き入りました
That's great, really. I was totally absorbed.
いや、よかったです、みんなよかったかな？
Yes, I'm glad. I hope everyone enjoyed it too?
よかったかな？どうでした？感想お願いしますね
Did you like it? How was it? Please share your thoughts!
ね、お願いします
Yes, please do!
じゃあ、ちょ、ちょ、そういうことで
Well, with that said...
そういうことで！ここで、1位にいったということは？
With that said! Since we reached number one, does that mean...
アズちゃんとアキちゃんのは？二人で歌うんじゃないですか？
...it's time for Azu-chan and Aki-chan? You two are going to sing, right?
歌っちゃいます！やります！
We sure will! We're doing it!
はい、お水飲もう
Yes, let's get some water first.
あ、ちょっとね、この間にうちはMCやるからさ、お水、お水
Oh, in the meantime, I'll handle the MC, so go get your water.
はい、ということでね、大神ミオチャンネルの大神ミオです！
All right, so, this is Ookami Mio from the Ookami Mio Channel!
よろしくお願いします！ということで
Please look after me! And so...
こんばんみお！
Good evening, Mio!
はい、こんばんみお！うち、うち、うちだよ！大神ミオだよ！
Yes, good evening, Mio! It's me, me, me! It's Ookami Mio!
これやってなかったからね
I hadn't done this intro yet.
ミオちゃん可愛い
Mio-chan, you're so cute.
ありがとう、助かる。あんま休憩してないんだよな、うち
Thank you, that helps. I haven't really had a break, actually.
茶々入れてんだよな、はい。というわけでね、皆さんもね、コメントいっぱいありがとうございます！
I've just been chiming in, haha. Anyway, thank you all so much for all the comments!
そしてRosaMIAアコースティックライブでね、トレンド1位にしていただいたということで、たくさんタグが賑わっていることでしょう！
And since we reached number one trending for the RosaMIA Acoustic Live, I'm sure the hashtag is super active right now!
後で感想見るのめっちゃ楽しみにしてます！
I'm really looking forward to reading your thoughts later!
というわけで、準備もよさそうなので
And with that, it looks like they're ready,
そろそろ聴いていただきましょうか？皆さん、では
so shall we have you listen to the next song? Everyone, are you...
皆さんの準備はいいですか？聴いていただきましょう、
...ready? Let's listen to...
「月のワルツ」
"Tsuki no Waltz."
こんなに月が青い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
mysterious things will happen.
どこか深い森の中で
Somewhere deep inside the forest,
さまよう私
I am wandering.
タキシード姿のウサギが来て
A rabbit in a tuxedo arrives,
ワインはいかがとテーブルへ
and invites me to a table for wine.
真っ赤なキノコの傘の下で
Under the cap of a bright red mushroom,
踊りが始まる
the dance begins.
あなたは...
You...
...どこにいるの
...where are you?
時間の国の迷子
A lost child in the land of time...
帰り道がわからないの
I don't know the way home.
待って 待っているのに
Even though I'm waiting, waiting...
眠れぬこの魂は
This sleepless soul...
あなたを捜し森の中
searches for you in the forest.
チャンドラマハルの王子様が
The prince of Chandra Mahal...
跪いて手を取る
kneels and takes my hand.
睫毛の長い蝶々たちが
Butterflies with long eyelashes...
シフォンのドレスでひらひらと
flutter about in chiffon dresses.
虹のタイツの甲虫は
Jewel beetles in rainbow tights...
剣のダンス
perform a sword dance.
求めるものはない
There is nothing to seek...
誘惑のラビリンス
in this labyrinth of temptation.
ミルク色の霧の彼方
Beyond the milk-colored mist,
確かな愛が欲しい
I want a love that is certain.
冷たいこの爪先を
My cold toes...
白鳥の羽で包んで
wrap them in swan feathers.
チャンドラマハルの王子様は
The prince of Chandra Mahal...
あなたに似た瞳で笑う
laughs with eyes that resemble yours.
満ちては欠ける
Waxing and waning,
宇宙を行く
traveling through space,
神秘の船
is the mysterious ship.
変わらないものなどないと
Whispering that nothing stays unchanged,
語りかけて
it speaks to me,
くるるよ
spinning around...
こんなに月が蒼い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
strange things will happen.
どこか見知らぬ森の中で
In some unfamiliar forest,
彷徨う私
I wander.
こんなに月が蒼い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
strange things will happen.
愛することは信じること
To love is to believe.
いつかその胸に抱かれ
Someday, held in those arms,
眠る夢を見る
I will dream of sleeping.
はい！
Yes!
ということで、
And with that...
「月のワルツ」でした！
...that was "Tsuki no Waltz"!
すごい良かったよ！
That was amazing!
「月のワルツ」でした！
That was "Tsuki no Waltz"!
素晴らしかった！
It was wonderful!
大、大変だった...
It... it was tough...
いや、あのさ、
But, you know...
うちはさ、やっぱ最初から、
Since I've known you guys from the very start...
二人が練習してるときから知ってるんだけど、
...and watched you practice,
今日、完成した感ない？
don't you feel like it was truly perfected today?
え、本当に？
Really?
えー、嬉しい！
Aww, I'm so happy!
あるよ！本当に！
Yes, indeed! Truly!
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
ハモりうまくなった。
Your harmony got so much better.
えー、嬉しい！やったー！
Aww, I'm so glad! Yay!
綺麗だった！
It was beautiful!
いやー、でもさ、
But, still...
緊張したよね、なんか。
we were really nervous, weren't we?聯盟
緊張したよね。ハモりでさ、入るところがいつもドキドキするって、アズキちゃんも言ってたよね。
We were. Azuki-chan, you also said you always get nervous about when to come in with the harmony, right?
うん、今回、アキちゃんメインでアズキがハモりで入らせてもらっているんですけど、
Yeah. This time, Aki-chan was on main and I did the harmony,
このハモりが、うー、ういゃーってなっちゃうの、練習の時。
but during practice, the harmony would always go all over the place.
だから練習した！
So we practiced a lot!
記憶...
My memory...
いや、めっちゃ練習したよね。
Yeah, we really practiced a ton.
確かに。
Indeed.
いや、もう本当にえらいなって、なんか感動しちゃった。
I was honestly so moved by how hard you worked.
えー、
Aww...
成長したよ、二人。
You two have really grown.
素晴らしいなって。
It's wonderful.
いや、いいハモりでしたね。
Yeah, it was a really nice harmony.
いや、ありがとうございました。
Thank you so much.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you.
本当にね。でも、なんかここで満足しちゃいけませんよ。
Indeed. But we shouldn't get complacent just yet.
ここで満足しちゃ、まだまだ。
We can't be satisfied here, we still have a long way to go.
だって、3人でさ、1曲しか歌ってないから。
After all, we've only sung one song together.
確かに！
True!
え、確かに！
Oh, that's true!
RosaMiAなのに。
Even though we're RosaMiA.
そうだよ。ここからね。
Exactly. It starts from here.
そうだよね。みんなもまだまだ、え、もう、ね、次何？次何？って。
Right. I'm sure everyone is thinking, "What's next? What's next?"
何でしょう？ 何だろうね？ 本当にね
What could it be? I wonder. Truly, isn't it?
ステージも綺麗で。なんかさっき、残ってませんでした？
The stage is so beautiful. Wasn't there something left earlier?
そうそう！もう今なくなっちゃったけど...
Right, right! It's gone now, but...
でもちゃんと出てて。「今日も月が綺麗ですね」って言ってくれてたから
But it was clearly there. A comment said, "The moon is beautiful tonight too."
そう、月のワルツのイメージでね
Yes, it fits the image of "The Moon Waltz".
そうなんです。月の波形に乗らせてもらいまして
That's right. We got to perform on the moon's waveform.
ここはなんか宇宙空間なんですかね？すごいステージだ
Is this place like outer space? It's an incredible stage.
綺麗だな。じゃあ、ちょっとね、そろそろ次の曲...
It's beautiful. Well then, it's about time for the next song...
次の曲いっちゃいます？いっちゃいますか？
Shall we move on to the next song? Shall we?
やばい、ちょっと緊張してお水飲みたいかも
Oh dear, I'm getting a bit nervous. I might need a drink of water.
緊張してきた。緊張してきた
I'm starting to get nervous. I really am.
大丈夫かな？よいしょ
I hope we'll be okay. Here we go.
いや、次の曲も結構ね、気合いが要るよね
Actually, the next song requires quite a bit of energy, doesn't it?
はい。気合いを入れまして...
Yes. Pumping myself up...
要ります。気合い要ります
It does. It takes a lot of effort.
お！あ！なんと！ステージがちょっと変わりまして
Oh! Ah! Wow! The stage has changed a bit!
綺麗な。このキューブはなんかちょっと懐かしくないですか？
How pretty. Doesn't this cube look a bit familiar?
見覚えが！見覚えがある！
Yes! I recognize this!
実はアキローゼの生誕祭で、二人に来てもらって歌わせてもらったとき
Actually, during Akirose's birthday stream, when I had you two sing with me...
最初に三人で歌わせてもらいましたときに、こういうキューブ状のステージで...
When the three of us first sang together, we were on a cube stage like this...
歌わせてもらったんだけど。なんかそれをちょっと彷彿とさせる
This really reminds me of that performance.
再現していただき。記念のキューブには、歌ったという記憶があります
They recreated it. I remember singing on this memorial cube.
え、それ歌うんですか？まさか、そんな！
Wait, are we singing that? No way!
何歌うんだろうね？何歌うんだろうね、結局ね
What are we going to sing? I wonder what we'll sing in the end.
そんな思い出もありますけれども。そうなんですよ
We have those memories, indeed.
実はね、まだ聴いてない方はよかったら聴いてみてください
Actually, if you haven't heard it yet, please check it out.
そうですね、チャンネルで上がってますね。そうです、そういうわけで
Right, it's uploaded on the channel. Yes, indeed.
ここから、なんと！
From here, actually...
2曲、連続で歌っていきます
...we will perform two songs in a row.
はい。ちょっと音を合わせさせてください、難しい曲なので
Yes. Please let us harmonize first, as it's a difficult song.
へえーーー
Heeeee...
Every day I listen to my heart ひとりじゃない
Every day I listen to my heart, I am not alone.
深い胸の奥で つながってる
Deep within my heart, we are connected.
果てしない時を越えて
Crossing over endless time...
輝く星が
...the shining stars...
出会えた奇跡 教えてくれる組合
...tell us of our miraculous meeting.
Every day I listen to my heart ひとりじゃない
Every day I listen to my heart, I am not alone.
この空の御胸に 抱かれて
Embraced in the bosom of this sky.
Wow oh yeah... Oh yeah...
私のこの両手で 何ができるの？
With these hands of mine, what can I do?
痛みに触れさせて そっと目を閉じて
Let me touch the pain, gently close your eyes.
夢を失うよりも 悲しいことは
More sorrowful than losing your dreams...
自分を信じてあげられないこと
...is being unable to believe in yourself.
愛を学ぶために 孤独があるなら
If loneliness exists for us to learn love,
意味のないことなど
then there is no such thing as meaningless...
...も恐れはしない
...I fear nothing.
心のしじまに 耳を澄まして
Listening closely to the silence of my heart,
私を呼んだなら どこへでも行くわ
If you call me, I will go anywhere.
あなたのその涙 私のものに
Let your tears become mine.
今は自分を 抱きしめて
Now, embrace yourself...
命のぬくもり 感じて
...and feel the warmth of life.
私たちは誰も ひとりじゃない
None of us are ever alone.
ありのままでずっと 愛されてる
We are always loved just as we are.
望むように生きて 輝く未来を
Live as you wish, toward a shining future.
いつまでも歌うわ あなたのために
I will sing forever, just for you.
私に還りなさい 記憶をたどり
Return to me, tracing your memory,
優しさと夢の水源へ
back to the source of gentleness and dreams,
もいちど星にひかれ 生まれるために
in order to be born again, led by the star.
魂のルフラン
It is the soul's refrain.
蒼い影につつまれた素肌が
The bare skin is covered by a blue shade,
時の中で 静かにふるえてる
trembling quietly in the passage of time.
命の行方を問いかけるように
As if asking where life has gone,
指先は私を求める
your fingertips seek for me.
抱きしめてた運命のあなたは
You, whom I held as my destiny,
季節に咲く まるではかない花
are like a fleeting flower blooming in season,
希望のにおいを胸に残して
leaving the scent of hope in my breast...
散り急ぐ あざやかな姿で
...as you rush to scatter in your vivid form.
な姿で
...vivid shape.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この手に還りなさい
Return to these arms,
めぐり逢うため
in order for us to meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen, again and again.
魂のルフラン
It is the soul's refrain.
祈るように まぶた閉じたときに
When I close my eyes as if praying,
世界はただ闇の底に消える
the world simply vanishes into the depths of darkness.
それでも鼓動は また動きだす
Yet my heartbeat starts to pulse once more,
限りある永遠を捜して
searching for a limited eternity.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
記憶をたどり
tracing your memories,
優しさと夢の水源へ
back to the source of gentleness and dreams.
あなたも還りなさい
You too must return,
愛しあうため
so that we may love one another.
心も体もくりかえす
The mind and body repeat themselves.
魂のルフラン
It is the soul's refrain.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この手に還りなさい
Return to these arms,
めぐり逢うため
in order for us to meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen, again and again.
魂のルフラン
It is the soul's refrain.
ということで
And with that...
はい
Yes!
2曲連続で聴いていただきました！
you just listened to two songs back-to-back!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
分かってるよ！分かってるよ！
I know, I know!
分かってる分かってる分かってる...
We know, we know...
自分が一番分かってるよね
You know it best yourself, right?
一緒に後ろ向いたら、このままなんか安心しちゃって
When we turned back together, I think I just got so relieved...
ちょっとやばい、これアキちゃんもしかして忘れてるかもと思って
I was like, "Oh no, did Aki-chan maybe forget?"
1フレーズ歌おうかなと思って一瞬迷ったんだけど、でも...
and hesitated for a second on whether to sing a phrase, but...
すみません...
I'm sorry...
途中から気づいたから！気づいたからよかった！
But I realized midway through! I'm glad I realized!
ギリギリ、セーフ...
It was a close, safe...
セーフ！セーフ！セーフ！
Safe, safe, safe!
セーフで片づけちゃっていいんじゃない？
Can we just call it safe and leave it at that?
やばい！
Oh no!
もう一回やろうぜはやばい
Saying "let's do it again" is too much!
もう一回やったっていいよ
It's fine to do it again!
はーい
Okay...
まあ、でもね、あの、皆さんすごくコメントの勢いがね、物語ってますよ
Well, but you know, everyone's comments are really telling!
「すごくかっこよかったよ」って言ってくれてるよ
They're saying, "It was so cool!"
ありがとう！
Thank you!
もう、これ、これが生の証明ですから
I mean, this is proof that it's live!
確かに、身を挺して証明してくれた！
True, you proved it by sacrificing yourself!
完全体はいつかまた、聞かせます
We'll let you hear the perfect version someday.
そう、完全体はね
Right, the perfect version!
成長コンテンツだからさ
Because we're a work-in-progress, after all!
いや、一度もこのさ、失敗さ、今までの練習でも一度もなかったんだよね！
I mean, we never once made this mistake during all our rehearsals!
なかった！どうして！
Never! Why now?!
本番の魔物が...
The monster of the live show...
怖いよー！
It's so scary!...
そんなことなかったのに、何でだろう
We never had that happen, I wonder why.
本番の魔物が来たね、これね
The monster of the live stage has arrived.
安心しちゃった、後ろ向いたら
I got too relieved when we turned around.
安心しちゃったんだね。あれ？って
You got relieved, huh? I was like, "Wait..."
全員、全員後ろ向いてる！って
Everyone is facing backwards!
「あれ？アキちゃん？」みたいな
Like, "Wait, Aki-chan?"
恥ずかしくて赤くなる顔が
My face turned red out of embarrassment...
はーい
Yes...
まあ、でもよかったです、はい
Well, but I'm glad anyway!
何とかね、あの、ここまでいっぱいに、練習してきた曲を披露できて、嬉しいなって思っているんですけれども
I'm just really happy we managed to show the song we've practiced so hard on.
ここでですね、
Now, at this point,
はい
Yes!
うちから、ちょっと、あの、お知らせというか、みんな知ってるんですけど、
I have a bit of an announcement to make. Well, everyone already knows, but...
なんと、大神ミオ、誕生日記念グッズ、発売中でございます！
Ookami Mio's Birthday Commemorative Goods are currently on sale!
まずお知らせ！こちらチェックしてみてくださーい！
First announcement! Please check this out!
スカジャンとですね、こちら、ら、キーホルダーですね、アクリルキーホルダーとなっております
We have a Sukajan jacket and... a keychain... an acrylic keychain, that is!
こちらです！こちら受注期間あと4日なので、
Here they are! The pre-order period has only 4 days left, so...
もうすぐじゃん！
That's so soon!
そう、あの、もし「買うの、あ、やべ、忘れてた」って人はね
Yes, so if anyone is like, "Oh crap, I forgot to buy it,"
あの、ちょっと早めに買っていただくと、というところではございます
we'd appreciate it if you could buy it a bit early.
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
はい。というわけで、ま、さらっとお知らせしちゃったんですけど
Yes. So, we've just gone through the announcements quickly,
もう一個ありますよね？ サムネイルに「告知あり」って
but there's one more, right? Since the thumbnail said "with announcement."
そう、告知はありましたけど、今日は3人の告知がなんと…
Yes, there was an announcement, but today we have an announcement for the three of us...
あるんですよ！／なんですか？ なんですか？
Yes, we do! / What is it? What is it?
いいですか？ 言っちゃって。／言っちゃって！
Is it okay to say it? / Go ahead and say it!
なんと！
Surprisingly...
RosaMiAの…
RosaMiA's...
ファーストシングルが！
first single...
デジタルリリースされます！
will be digitally released!
タイトルは「Blossom Sinfonia」でございます！
The title is "Blossom Sinfonia"!
オリジナル楽曲ですね！／そう、オリジナル楽曲なんですよ！
It's our original song! / Yes, it's an original song, surprisingly!
我々RosaMiAのファーストシングルということで
As RosaMiA's very first single,
最初にふさわしい、3人の声が咲き誇るような楽曲に、そしてRosaMiAロードも咲き誇るように
it's a fitting start where our three voices bloom, hoping our path forward will also bloom...
そんな華やかな、1曲目。
making it such a gorgeous first song.
かなり華やかとなっておりますね。
It has turned out to be very gorgeous indeed.
大事に育てていきたい曲ですし、みんなに愛される曲になってくれたら嬉しいです
We want to cherish and nurture this song, and we hope it will be loved by everyone.
この後、24時から、
So tonight, starting from midnight...
各配信サイトでダウンロードできますので、ぜひ聴いてくださいね！
it will be available on various platforms, so please listen to it!
でも、この曲がどんな曲か気になりますよね？
But you must be curious about what kind of song this is, right?
イメージ画像だけで、どんな曲なんだろう？ 華やか？
You've only seen the illustration, so you might wonder. Is it gorgeous?
華やか？ うん、わかるかな、わからないかな。
Gorgeous? Yeah, we wonder if you can tell.
みんな聴いたいよね？
Everyone wants to hear it, right?
聴きたい！ 聴きたい！
We want to hear it! We want to hear it!
みんなのコメントを読んでいます。
I'm reading everyone's comments.
その間に水飲もう、水飲もう。
Let's drink some water in the meantime.
「イラストいい」「ビジュいい」ありがとう。気になる、マジで。
"The illustration is nice," "the visual is nice," thank you! "Curious, seriously."
ホロ鳥来るか？ ホロ鳥さん、どうですか？
"Will Holo-tori come?" What about Holo-tori?
どうなんですか、ホロ鳥さん。実際どうですか？
What do you think, Holo-tori? How is it actually?
ちょっとあきちゃんもお水飲みます。
Aki-chan is going to drink some water too.
そうだね、あきちゃん、お水飲んで来てね。
Yeah, Aki-chan, go drink some water.
いや、気になるよね。
But you're curious, right?
ということでね、なんとこの後…
And so, actually, after this...
お披露目しちゃうかもしれないっていうお話。
we might just perform it.
これは最後まで見逃せない。
You can't miss this until the very end.
見逃せないってこと？
You mean we can't miss it?
というわけで、なんとこの後、生歌唱にて初お披露目させていただきます！
So, actually, after this, we will perform it live for the first time!
いや、ハードル高くないですか？／心落ち着けて。
Wait, isn't the hurdle too high? / Calm down.
あのね、1回説明しておきたいんですけど、この曲、歌唱難易度がバチ高くて
No, you see, I want to explain that this song is extremely difficult to sing.
今まで歌ってきた中で、たぶん1番の最難関歌となっております。
Out of all the songs we've sung so far, this is probably the hardest.
この曲、いっちゃん最初に練習し始めたもんね？
We started practicing this song first, didn't we?
どの曲よりも1番練習した。
We practiced it more than any other song.
1番練習したけど、それでもなお難しい。
We practiced it the most, but it's still difficult.
これから聴いてもらうけどさ、
We're about to perform it for you now...
こういうハモリが好きな人もいると思うから
I think some of you might like these kinds of harmonies,
どうやって歌ってんだろうみたいな
wondering how it's structured or how we're singing it.
細かいところまで聴いていただけたら嬉しい。
We'd be happy if you could listen closely to the details.
じゃあ、今日24時、この後デジタルリリースされる曲となります。
So, this is the song that will be digitally released tonight.
もういいですか？ 行っちゃって。／ちょっと順番があるでしょ。
Is it okay to go now? / Wait, there's a proper order to things.
大丈夫？／あきちゃんは大丈夫じゃないよ。
Are you okay? / Aki-chan is not okay at all.
嘘でしょ？／ちょっと大丈夫になろうよ、頑張って。
No way! / Come on, let's pull ourselves together and do our best!
大丈夫だよ、心配しないでね。
You'll be fine, don't worry.
今までの練習の成果を発揮すればいい。練習してきたもん。
Just show the results of all our practice up to now. We've got this.
はい、というわけで。
All right, here we go.
行きますよ。それでは聴いてください。
Here we go. Please listen to it.
せーの、Blossom Sinfonia！
One, two, "Blossom Sinfonia"!
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
To you in the distance, so that my song reaches...
今宵におびえる 私がいる
Fearing this night, here I am.
それでも明日に 期待している
Even so, I still hope for tomorrow.
あの日に見つけた 奇跡の種
The seed of a miracle that I found on that day.
いつでもそこには希望がある
There is always hope waiting there
暗くても一筋さす
Even in the darkness, a single ray shines through
明日への光へと
Towards the light of tomorrow...
手を伸ばしてる今でも
we are still reaching out, even now.
途切れないように繋いできたから
Because we have kept it connected so it won't break,
今芽吹き始めた未来があるの
there is a future that has now begun to bud.
遠くのあなたに歌届くように
So that our song may reach you far away,
この先も紡ぐの
we will continue to spin our story.
Ah...
大事に抱えた希望の芽は
The bud of hope we cherished so dearly
か弱く儚い それでもいい
is fragile and fleeting, but that's alright.
いつの日か小さくても
One day, even if it is small...
重なれば鮮やかに染め上げられる世界を
If they overlap, we can dye the world in vivid colors.
信じた未来へ歩いてきたから
Because we have walked towards the future we believed in,
今手を取り合える仲間がいるの
we now have friends we can hold hands with.
遠くのあなたの手も握れるように
So that we can also hold your hand far away,
花は今色づく
the flowers are starting to color now.
不安でも大丈夫と
Even if we're anxious, saying "it's okay,"
挫けても続けてきた
even if we faltered, we kept moving forward.
弱くてもいい 怖くてもいい
It's okay to be weak, it's okay to be afraid.
届けると決めたんだ 心に響け あなたへ
We've decided to deliver it, let it echo in your heart.
途切れないように繋いできたから
Because we have kept it connected so it won't break,
今鮮やかなほど咲き誇る花
the flowers are now blooming so vividly.
遠くのあなたに歌届くように
So that our song may reach you far away,
変わらないよ ずっと
it will never change, forever.
何があっても ずっと
No matter what happens, forever,
あなたへと紡ぐの
we will spin our story for you.
本日24時よりデジタルリリース！
Digital release starts today at midnight!
ぜひみんなRosaMiAのファーストシングル聞いてね！
Please make sure to listen to RosaMiA's first single!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
頑張った！頑張った！
We did it! We did our best!
告知あり
[Announcement]